[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which is the largest national park in the United States?",
    "options": [
      "Wrangell–St. Elias",
      "Yellowstone",
      "Yosemite",
      "Grand Canyon"
    ],
    "answer": "Wrangell–St. Elias"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "In which country is Banff National Park located?",
    "options": [
      "Canada",
      "United States",
      "Australia",
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which national park is famous for its geysers and hot springs?",
    "options": [
      "Yellowstone",
      "Serengeti",
      "Kruger",
      "Yosemite"
    ],
    "answer": "Yellowstone"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which national park is known for the giant sequoia trees?",
    "options": [
      "Sequoia National Park",
      "Yellowstone",
      "Grand Canyon",
      "Everglades"
    ],
    "answer": "Sequoia National Park"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Where is the Serengeti National Park located?",
    "options": [
      "Tanzania",
      "Kenya",
      "South Africa",
      "Botswana"
    ],
    "answer": "Tanzania"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which national park is home to the famous Half Dome rock formation?",
    "options": [
      "Yosemite National Park",
      "Zion National Park",
      "Grand Teton",
      "Rocky Mountain"
    ],
    "answer": "Yosemite National Park"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which national park is famous for its large population of polar bears?",
    "options": [
      "Wapusk National Park",
      "Yellowstone",
      "Banff",
      "Denali"
    ],
    "answer": "Wapusk National Park"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which national park is located in the Australian Outback?",
    "options": [
      "Uluru-Kata Tjuta National Park",
      "Kruger National Park",
      "Banff National Park",
      "Fiordland National Park"
    ],
    "answer": "Uluru-Kata Tjuta National Park"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which national park is known for its diverse coral reefs?",
    "options": [
      "Great Barrier Reef Marine Park",
      "Everglades",
      "Banff",
      "Yellowstone"
    ],
    "answer": "Great Barrier Reef Marine Park"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which national park features the Grand Canyon?",
    "options": [
      "Grand Canyon National Park",
      "Zion National Park",
      "Bryce Canyon",
      "Arches National Park"
    ],
    "answer": "Grand Canyon National Park"
  }
]